[HANNAH] I stalked
Mr. Jeon for a few days.
I'm pretty sure
the necklace is in his room.
I just need to find it!
For Mom.
I need a full background
check on her.
[DANIEL] Can you handle it?
- Yes, sir.
- Good.
Thank you, sir.
[HANNAH] Good morning.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Where is it?!
[CLICKS TONGUE] Tsk.
It should be
around here somewhere.
Where could it possibly be?!
Is it here?
[DANIEL] Looking for something?
[PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GASPS] That's mine!
- Give that back!
- You couldn't afford this.
Where did you steal this from?
I never stole that! You're
so judgmental! Give it back!
Give it back, please! I need
to pawn that to help my mom!
[GASPS]
Filipinos...
always about the money.
How much will it take
to make you talk?
I don't want your money!
You racist!
[SENSUAL MUSIC PLAYING]
What did you say?
Um...
Rac..
[SENSUAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Ah, Annyeonghaseyo, Mr.--
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Jeon...